☆独家制作☆
喜马拉雅主播 & 微信公众号:
美国青少年英语
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
[DISTORTED CHEERING]
[YELLING AND CHEERING]
["R.O.C.K. IN THE U.S.A." PLAYING]
克莱恩镇长呈现  欢乐园游会
♪ Rockin' in the U.S.A. ♪
[SQUEALING AND LAUGHING]
♪ Hey! R.O.C.K. in the U.S.A... ♪
- [MAN] One for each of you. - Thanks.
-一人一个  -谢谢
[VENDOR] Have fun.
祝你们愉快
♪ R.O.C.K. in the U.S.A. ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Rockin' in the U.S.A. ♪
- [MAN 2] There you go. - Yeah!
-给你  -好啊
["THE WASHINGTON POST MARCH" PLAYING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
- [BAND STOPS] - Now, doesn't that just lift your spirits?
令人精神振奋吧
[CHEERING]
Let's give another big hand for the Hawkins High Marching Band!
我们再为霍金斯高中军乐队鼓鼓掌吧
[CHEERING]
I hope you're all having a good time tonight.
希望大家今晚玩得愉快
- [CROWD CHEERS] - Are you having a good time?
你们玩得愉快吗
[CHEERING]
[LARRY] I can't hear you!
我听不见
Are you having a good time?
你们玩得愉快吗
[LOUD CHEERING]
[CHUCKLES] I want you to know that we spared no expense
我想告诉大家  我们不惜重金
to provide you with the very best entertainment that money can buy!
向大家呈现 钱能买到的最好的娱乐
[FAIR WORKER] Keep your arms inside.
手臂放在里面
Uh-oh! Dad can't get out now.
爸爸这下别想跑了
Why do you two enjoy torturing me?
你俩为什么喜欢折磨我
- Because it's fun. - Yeah, Dad, 'cause it's fun!
-因为好玩啊  -是啊  爸爸  因为好玩
- Oh, here we go. - [TED GROANS]
我们走咯
[TED] Oh, boy.
天呐
Hoo!
But enough of me blabbering.
我不再废话了
Who here wants to see some fireworks?
谁想看看焰火
[CHEERING]
Come on, now, you can do better than that.
拜托  这样的热情怎么行
Who here wants to see some fireworks?
谁想看看焰火
[LOUD CHEERING]
克莱恩镇长  罗恩县园游会
["SEMPER FIDELIS" PLAYING]
[KAREN SIGHS]
Uh, why are we stopping?
我们怎么停了
Because I slipped Jimmy a five.
我给吉姆塞了五块钱
You what?
什么
Come on, these are the best seats in the house.
拜托  这可是最棒的座位
The best seats in the house.
最棒的座位
- [FIREWORKS POPPING] - Oh!
Happy Fourth of July!
国庆节快乐
[CHEERING]
[KAREN] Whoa!
[LAUGHING]
- That was pretty, wasn't it? - Yeah.
-好看吧  -嗯
Yeah.
是啊
[KAREN GASPS]
[OMINOUS SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[RUSTLING IN TREES]
Mom, the trees.
妈妈  树
- What, baby? - The trees are moving.
-怎么了  宝贝  -树在动
[RUSTLING CONTINUES]
Why are you looking at the trees, baby?
你为什么看树啊  宝贝
The fireworks. Look at the fireworks!
看焰火啊  看焰火
[KAREN LAUGHS] That was a big one, wasn't it?
那个好大  是吧
[THUDDING FOOTSTEPS]
[CREATURE SNARLING]
[THEME SONG PLAYING]
怪奇物语  第三季 第七集
第七章
咬伤
[FIREWORKS POPPING AND CRACKLING DISTANTLY]
[CROWD CHEERING DISTANTLY]
[MARCHING BAND PLAYING DISTANTLY]
[ELEVEN] He said he was building something.
他说他在建造什么
That it was all for me.
还说都是为了我
Building something...
建造什么
- Is he talking about the flayed? - He must be.
-是指失灵者吗  -肯定是
So, he's building an army, just like we thought.
所以他跟我们猜的一样  在组建大军
Yeah, but he's not building this army to spread.
是啊  但他不是为了扩散
He's building it to stop Eleven.
是为了抵抗十一
Last year, El closed the gate on him.
去年  一一把他关在了门里
I have a feeling that really pissed him off.
我猜这让他很生气
Like, royally.
非常生气
And the Mind Flayer now knows that
吸灵魔现在知道
she's the only thing that can stop him.
她是唯一能阻止他的人
- But if she's out of the way... - Game over.
-但如果她被除掉了  -完蛋
He also said
他还说
he was gonna kill all of you.
他要杀了你们所有人
Yeah, well, that's nice.
真好啊
[FAINT SCREECHING NOISE]
[OMINOUS SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you guys hear that?
你们听到了吗
[NANCY SHUDDERS]
It's just the fireworks.
只是焰火
Billy...
比利
When he told you this, it was here, in this room?
他跟你说这话时  他在这里  这个房间里
[DISTANT THUDDING NOISE]
[FLUTTERING SOUND]
He knows we're here.
他知道我们在哪了
[TREES RUSTLING]
[CREATURE SNARLS]
[CREATURE SCREECHES]
[ALARM BLARING]
[SLURRING] Jesus, slow down!
天呐  慢点
[SLURRING] Yeah, what is this, like, the Indy 500?
是啊  这是印第安纳波利斯500英里大奖赛吗
It's the Indy 300.
是300
- No, dingus, it's 500! - It's 300!
-不  呆瓜  是500  -是300
Let's say a million.
一百万好了
[BOTH LAUGHING LOUDLY]
- What is wrong with them? - I don't know.
-他们怎么了  -我不知道
- [ERICA] Dustin, watch out! - [DUSTIN] Shit!
-达斯汀  小心  -该死
[STEVE GRUNTS, YELLS]
- Oh! - [ROBIN GROANS]
You guys all right back there?
你们没事吧
[BOTH GROANING]
They're fine.
他们没事
Come on. We gotta go, now.
快  我们得走了
- Come on! Get out! - Let's go!
-快出来  -下来
[STEVE] Ow!
- [STEVE] We're coming! - Here goes nothin'.
-我们来了  -试试便知了
- [STEVE] This sucks. - [BEEPING]
真讨厌
[ROBIN AND STEVE WHOOPING GIDDILY]
- Hey! You look like you're surfing! - Surfing! Yeah!
-你就像在冲浪  -冲浪  是啊
[STEVE] Whoa!
- They seem drunk. - Why would they be drunk?
-他们像是醉了  -他们怎么会醉了
I'm a natural! Check it out!
我有天赋  看啊
Whoop!
[ROBIN LAUGHS]
Wipeout!
翻车了
[BOTH LAUGHING]
- He's burning up. - [STEVE] You're burning up.
-他在发烧  -你在发烧
- One sec, one sec. Steve, Steve. - [STEVE] God, no.
-别动  史蒂夫  -天呐  不
Ow!
His pupils are super dilated.
他的瞳孔完全放大了
Maybe he's drugged.
或许他被下了药
Ugh. Boop!
Steve, are you drugged?
史蒂夫  你被下药了吗
How many times, Dad?
说几次啊  爸爸
I don't do drugs. It's only marijuana.
我不嗑药  我只吸大麻
This isn't funny, okay? I need to know what they did to you.
这可不好玩  我需要知道他们对你做了什么
- Are you gonna die on us? - Boop.
-你们会死吗  -波波
We all die, my strange little child friend.
我们都会死  小怪孩朋友
It's just a matter of how...
重点是怎么死
and when.
什么时候死
They're gonna be looking for us up there,
上面的人会在找我们
so I need you to tell me where you parked your car.
我需要你告诉我  你把车停在了哪
Oh, can we make a pit stop at the food court?
我们可以去美食街停留一下吗
- I would kill for a hot dog on a stick. - Ooh!
我太想吃热狗棒了
All right. Yeah, food.
好  好  食物
Yes, you can have as much food as you want,
你想吃多少吃多少
but only if you tell me where your car is parked.
但你必须告诉我你把车停哪了
- Uh-oh. - Uh-oh?
The car's off the board.
车开不了了
- What? - They took the keys.
-什么  -他们拿走了车钥匙
The Russians, they took the keys.
苏联人  他们拿走了钥匙
Like, forever ago.
好久之前了
[ROBIN AND STEVE LAUGH]
That's a bummer, right?
真糟糕  是吧
[ROBIN LAUGHING]
[ROBIN AND STEVE] Oh!
Oh, my God, that tastes so good. Ah!
LYNX运输
天呐  味道太好了
Steve, can you taste the air?
史蒂夫  你尝到空气的味道了吗
I taste it! I taste it!
是啊  尝到了
- Stop! - Shit! Come on! Come on!
-站住  -该死  快跑
- [KIDS CLAMORING] - [IN RUSSIAN] Stop right there!
快站住
- [ROBIN] Okay, okay, okay! Woo! - Why are we running?
-好好好  -我们跑什么
[ROBIN LAUGHING]
[ELEVEN GRUNTING]
[MIKE] Yeah. That's good like that.
嗯  这样就行
Hey, get away from the windows.
远离窗户
[ALL PANTING]
[LAMP SQUEAKING]
[RUMBLING]
[ELECTRIC CRACKLING]
[GASPING]
[BREATHING RAPIDLY]
It's close.
靠近了
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
[BRANCHES SNAPPING]
[RUMBLING FOOTSTEPS]
[GLASSES CLINKING]
[RUMBLING STOPS]
Where'd it go?
它去哪了
[NANCY EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SHUDDERING BREATHS]
- [CREATURE SHRIEKS] - [ALL GASPING]
[YELLS, GRUNTS]
- [CREATURE SHRIEKS] - [JONATHAN GRUNTS]
[JONATHAN YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
- [SHRIEKS] - [JONATHAN GROANS]
[SHRIEKS]
[CREATURE WAILS, SCREECHES]
[CREATURE WAILS]
[SHRIEKING IN PAIN]
[GASPS]
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
[CREATURE SCREAMS]
[ELEVEN YELLS]
[CREATURE SHRIEKS]
[MAX YELPS]
Holy shit.
我去
[SHRIEKING]
- [GLASS SHATTERS] - [SHRIEKING]
[PANTING]
[CREATURES SHRIEKING]
[SHRIEKING AND BARKING]
[YELLS]
- [WHIMPERING SHRIEKS] - [PANTING]
[ROARING AND SHRIEKING]
[ELEVEN SCREAMS]
El!
一一
[SCREAMING]
[MIKE] El!
- [ALL GRUNTING] - [CREATURE ROARING]
[PUMPS SHOTGUN]
[ROARING]
[MIKE] Pull!
拉啊
[JONATHAN] Nancy, shoot it!
南茜  开枪
[SCREAMING]
[SNARLING]
[PAINED SNARLS]
[ELEVEN SCREAMS]
[MAX] Come on! Lucas!
快  卢卡斯
[NANCY PUMPS SHOTGUN]
[YELLS]
[ROARS]
[LUCAS GRUNTS, YELLS]
[SHOTGUN FIRES]
[ROARING]
[SCREAMING]
- [KIDS STRAINING] - [CREATURE ROARS]
[YELLS]
[MAX] Pull!
拉
- [SHOTGUN FIRES] - [CREATURE SCREECHES]
- [SQUELCHING] - [ROARING]
El! El, you okay?
一一  你没事吧
[CREATURE ROARING]
[SHRIEKING]
[SCREECHING IN PAIN]
[MONSTROUS CHITTERING]
[CREATURE SNARLS]
[PANTING HEAVILY]
[ROARING]
[ELEVEN PANTING]
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
[ROARING]
[YELLING]
[PAINED SCREECHING]
[YELLS]
[DISTANT ROARING]
- [NANCY] Go, go, go! - [JONATHAN] Come on, come on, go!
-快走  -快走
- [NANCY] Go! - [JONATHAN] Hurry up! Come on!
-快走  -快  快
[MIKE] Everybody out!
大家快出去
- [JONATHAN] Go! - [NANCY] Go, come on!
-快走  -快
- [CREATURE ROARS] - [JONATHAN] Go, go, go, go!
走走走
- [LUCAS] Come on! - [NANCY REPEATING] Come on!
-快走  -快
[LUCAS] Come on! Come on!
快  快
[CREATURE SHRIEKING]
[JONATHAN] Get in. Right here.
上去  快走
[ELEVEN WAILS IN PAIN]
- Drive! Drive! - [ENGINE STARTING]
开车  开车
[ROARING]
- [STEVE] Whoa! - Where are we going?
我们去哪
- Just trust me. - [ROBIN LAUGHS]
相信我
All clear.
安全
[SCORE FROM BACK TO THE FUTURE PLAYING]
[MARTY] Doc!
博士
What did I tell you?!
我怎么跟你说的
Eighty-eight miles per hour!
时速88英里
[DUSTIN] Come on.
来
- [METAL CLANGING IN MOVIE] - [DOC GASPS]
[DOC] The temporal displacement occurred exactly 1:20...
时间错位发生在1:20整
- You two, sit. - No, no, no! These seats are too close!
-你俩  坐下  -不不  这座位太近了
- Dude, these seats blow. - Then don't watch the movie.
-哥们  这座位太烂了  -那就别看电影
- We wanna watch it. - Then watch it!
-我们想看  -那就看啊
- Shh! - Shh!
Sorry.
抱歉
Whatever you do,
不管怎样
don't... go... anywhere.
别去别的地方
- Fine, Dad. - [ROBIN SNICKERS]
好吧  爸爸
[DOC] The appropriate question is "When the hell are they?"
该问的问题是"他们在哪个时间"
You see, Einstein has just become
瞧  爱因斯坦刚成为
- the world's first time traveler! - Sorry. Sorry.
-世界首个时间旅行者  -抱歉
- [DOC] I sent him... into the future! - [DUSTIN SIGHS]
我把他  送去了未来
Okay, it's official.
好了  正式决定了
I'm never having kids.
我绝对不要孩子
- What are we doing here? - We're laying low.
-我们来这里干什么  -躲藏
Cooling off.
等风头过去
Like Oswald.
就像奥斯瓦尔德[刺杀肯尼迪的凶手]
Oswald was found in a theater and shot to death.
奥斯瓦尔德在影院里被抓到  还被打死了
A week later.
那是一周后了
The point is, his plan didn't work.
重点是  他的计划没成功
Only because it was a setup.
那是因为是个陷阱
- What? - He was just a patsy.
-什么  -他就是个替罪羊
- Tell me you're joking. - Shh!
你开玩笑的吧
[ERICA AND DUSTIN] Shh!
We need to get outta here.
我们得离开这里
All right, you watch Tweedledee and Tweedledum.
好吧  你看着那俩傻蛋
- Make sure they don't go anywhere. - Where are you going?
-别让他们乱跑  -你去哪
To find us a ride.
找辆车
[DOC] Look out!
小心
[DELOREAN ZAPPING]
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
[MARTY] Doc...
博士
- What's happening? - I have no idea.
-怎么回事  -我不知道
[MARTY] Are you telling me that you built a time machine...
你是说你建了台时光机
[ALEXEI SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
- What's he saying? - He's showing me the location of the key
-他在说什么  -他在给我指关掉机器的
to turn off the machine.
钥匙的位置
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
- Sorry, "keys". Two keys. - [ALEXEI SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
抱歉  有两把钥匙
Two-man rule.
两人规则
- Two-man rule? - Yeah, two men, two keys, like a...
-什么  -对  两人  两把钥匙
nuclear launch.
就像核武发射
But, uh, to retrieve the keys, there is a vault.
但要拿到钥匙  需要进入地库
- [SPEAKING RUSSIAN] - And to open the vault,
要打开地库
you need to enter Planck's constant.
需要输入普朗克常数
- Planck's what? - Planck's constant.
-普朗克什么  -普朗克常数
- It's a very famous number. - All right, so we get the keys,
-一个著名的数字  -好  那我们拿到钥匙
and then we turn the machine off.
然后关掉机器
That's what he says.
他就是这么说的
All right, well, that shouldn't be too hard. We can do this.
好  应该不太难  我们可以的
Joyce, did you hear the part where he said the place was like
乔伊  你听到他说那里就像
an impenetrable fortress?
固若金汤的城堡了吧
Yeah, but there has to be a way in.
是啊  但肯定也有进路的
Yeah, there is. Our military.
是啊  有  我们的军队
- Who are coming. - Well, we don't know that anymore
-他们要来了  -我们不能确定
because you yelled at them like it was a parent-teacher conference,
因为你吼了他们 就好像那是家长会似的
and then you hung up on them, so
然后还挂了他们的电话
we don't know what the hell's going on,
所以  我们不能确定现在的情况
because now we're... Wait, wait, what are we do... Oh!
因为我们  等等  我们在干什么...
Wait, that's right!
等等  对了
We're on our way to rescue our children
我们正要去营救我们的孩子
from the big, bad Fourth of July celebration!
因为大坏国庆节庆典要害他们
You know what, if you can't handle this, then just turn around
知道吗  如果你受不了  那就调头
and drop me off first.
先让我下车吧
What are you gonna do?
你要做什么
You gonna walk back to Hawkins?
你要走回霍金斯吗
I will do anything if it gets me away from you!
只要能远离你  我干什么都行
Children! Children! Children!
孩子们  孩子们
This interminable bickering was amusing at first,
这无休无止的斗嘴起初还算有趣
but it's getting very stale
但越来越烦人了
and we've still got a long drive ahead of us.
我们还要开很久的车呢
So, why don't you two cut the horseshit
所以  你俩就少说屁话
and get to the part where you admit
直接承认
your sexual feelings for one another?
你们对彼此的性吸引吧
- Whoa! - You are way off base, buddy!
你扯太远了
Oh, spare me, spare me, spare me!
少来了
Yes, yes, he's a brute. I know.
是的  他很野蛮  我知道
Probably reminds you of a bad relationship,
大概让你回忆起了不好的旧爱
and, gosh, you'd really like a nice man to settle down with,
天呐  你很想找个好男人安顿下来
but, admit it,
但承认吧
you're real curious to know what he's like in the sack.
你很想知道他在床上什么样
And you. Ha!
还有你
Well, you're just a big manbaby
你就是个大巨婴
who'd rather act tough than show his true feelings,
宁可逞强  也不愿袒露真心
because the last time you opened your heart, you got hurt.
因为上次你敞开心扉时  你受了伤
Owie.
And now, rather than admit these feelings,
现在  你们不愿承认你们的感情
you're dancing around one another
而是跟彼此周旋
with this mind-numbing and frankly boorish mating ritual.
上演着令人麻痹的笨拙交配仪式
So, please, for my sake,
拜托  为了我
either quit your bickering, or pull over,
你们要么别吵了  要么靠边停
tear off those clothes,
脱掉衣服
and get it over with already!
赶紧发泄完拉倒
[GASPS]
[DEEP SIGH]
[IN RUSSIAN] What was that?
你说什么了
[IN RUSSIAN] I told them they should have sex.
我说他们该做爱
They have not had sex?
他们还没做过爱吗
No.
没有
[SNICKERS]
[CHUCKLES]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[JOYCE MUTTERS]
[ALEXEI SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[MURRAY LAUGHS] Oh! Oh!
[MURRAY AND ALEXEI CONTINUE LAUGHING]
欢迎来到印第安纳州
[TIRES SQUEALING]
布拉德利大块头
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[ELEVEN GROANS]
外用酒精
纱布
Okay, get her down.
好  扶她坐下
[NANCY] Okay.
好
Lemme see.
我看看
- Oh, shit. - [GROANS]
该死
What... What... Hey, what are you doing?
你干什么
I'm cleaning the wound.
清理伤口
No, first, we need to stop the bleeding,
不  首先得止血
then clean, then disinfect, then bandage.
然后清理  然后消毒  然后缠绷带
I skateboard. Trust me.
我滑滑板  相信我
Mike, hold this.
迈克  摁住
[GROANS]
Keep the pressure on it, nice and firm, okay?
稳稳地压好
We're gonna need water, soap.
我们需要水  肥皂
- Yeah, okay. - All right.
-好的  -好
Does any of this help?
这些东西有用吗
No.
没用
Go get me a washcloth and a bowl.
去找条毛巾和碗来
- A bowl? - Lucas.
-碗  -卢卡斯
- Go. - [STAMMERS] Okay.
-快去  -好
[GROANS]
[NANCY] What did that thing look like to you?
你觉得那玩意像什么
Like that thing in the hospital, only bigger.
像医院的那个  但更大了
Yeah, a lot bigger.
是啊  大多了
Like, Tom and Bruce, they merged to become one, right?
汤姆和布鲁斯  他们合并成了一个  是吧
And... And Driscoll kept saying
德里斯科尔一直说
how she needed to go back to the source...
她得回到源头去
Wait, you think Driscoll's in there?
等等  你觉得那里面有德里斯科尔吗
Maybe.
可能吧
And... And... And maybe Heather
可能还有海瑟  珍妮特
and Janet, too, and God knows who else.
天知道还有谁
I don't know how we're gonna kill this thing, but if we do...
我不知道我们要怎么杀了那玩意  但如果杀了他
- We kill all the flayed. - And... we end this.
-失灵者也都会死  -我们能了结此事
Maybe.
或许吧
All I know is...
我只知道
we need El.
我们需要一一
[LUCAS] Bowl...
碗
Bowl...
- Why wouldn't it be with the cereal? - I don't know.
-怎么会在燕麦片区  -我不知道
What else do you use a bowl for?
你还用碗做什么
I... I don't know.
我不知道
[LUCAS SIGHS]
Oh, shit.
该死
Satan's Baby.
撒旦之子
You ever shot one of these suckers?
烟花
你发射过这玩意吗
No. Is it sweet?
没有  厉害吗
- That's an understatement. - [MAX] That doesn't look like a bowl.
-可不止呢  -那可不像碗
Nah, it's way better.
不  这好多了
There is a reason this warning label says "18 or older".
这玩意标注"18岁以上"是有原因的
This sucker is filled with 150 grains of black powder.
这玩意有150克黑火药
AKA gunpowder.
也就是火药
Strap two of these together, and it's bigger than an M-80.
把俩绑在一起  比M80还厉害
Five of them,
五个
we've got ourselves a stick of dynamite.
就赶得上炸药了
You wanna kill that thing with fireworks?
你想拿烟花杀了那玩意
Do you have a better idea?
你有更好的主意吗
Uh, yeah. Eleven.
有  十一
Against that thing? She's gonna need some backup.
对付那玩意吗  她会需要支援的
- Oh, my God. - [LUCAS SCOFFS]
天呐
Hold this.
拿着
[MIKE GROANS]
Does that hurt?
疼吗
Uh, not bad.
还行
You're gonna have an awesome scar.
你会留个很酷的疤
You'll look even more badass.
你看上去会更厉害
Bitchin'.
贱样
Yeah, bitchin'.
对  贱样
[CHUCKLES]
El...
一一
Yeah?
怎么
I've been meaning to tell you something.
我有话想对你说
It's just, being broken up,
分手
it's been hard.
让我好难受
[DISTORTED RADIO CHATTER]
And...
我...
I like that you and Max are friends now.
很高兴你和麦克斯成了朋友
It's just, I was jealous at first, and... and angry.
但起初  我嫉妒了  生气了
And that's why I said all that stupid stuff.
所以我才说了那些蠢话
And it's like I wanted you all to myself.
我希望独占你
And now I realize how unfair that is.
现在我意识到  这是不公平的
And selfish. And, like... I'm sorry.
自私的  我...很抱歉
I just, like, I've never felt like this,
我从未有过这样的感觉
you know, with anyone before...
对任何人都没有
and...
所以
[SIGHS] You know, they do say it makes you crazy.
人说这让你疯狂
What makes you crazy?
什么让你疯狂
You never... You never heard that term...
你没听过那句话吗
You know, like the phrase, like...
就是那个说法
"blank makes you crazy", like the word...
"...让你疯狂"  就是那个词
- "Girlfriends"? - No, no, no, no, not... not girlfriends.
"女友"吗  -不不不  不是女友
- "Boyfriends". - No! No, no, not boyfriends either.
-"男友"  -不不不  不是男友
- It's like... It's like a feeling or... - [SOFTLY] A feeling...
-是...一种感觉  -感觉
Yeah, like something...
对  就像...
Like, old people say it to each other sometimes.
老人有时会对彼此说那个
- Old people? - Yeah.
-老人  -对
What I wanna say is...
我想说的是
that I just...
我...
I know that I...
我知道我...
- [DUSTIN SPEAKING VIA RADIO, GARBLED] - [STATIC POPPING]
[DUSTIN, DISTORTED VIA RADIO] I repeat... this is a code red!
重复  红色警报
- [SCORE FROM BACK TO THE FUTURE PLAYS] - Dustin?
Mike?
达斯汀
迈克
- [MIKE] Dustin! - Mike!
-达斯汀  -迈克
Oh, my God, you have to listen. I know I've been MIA,
天呐  听好了  我知道我玩失踪了
and I'm sorry, it's not because I'm mad.
抱歉  不是因为我生气了
I mean, I actually was mad,
我是生气了
but it's also because I was trapped underground
但也是因为  我被困在了地下
in a secret Russian base.
在一个秘密苏联基地里
[GARBLED RADIO AUDIO]
Dustin, you're going way too fast. I can't understand you.
达斯汀  你说太快了  我听不懂
I know that sounds insane,
我知道听上去很疯狂
but the Russians have infiltrated Hawkins!
但苏联人渗透进了霍金斯
The goddamn Russians!
苏联人啊
And now... they're using... to open the gate.
他们还用...开启入口
Dustin, you're... you're breaking up.
达斯汀  你信号不好
And now they're after us and we don't have a way out of here,
他们在追杀我们  我们没有出路
so I need you to come and get us. Can Nancy drive?
我需要你们来救我们  南茜能开车吗
[GARBLED RADIO AUDIO]
Dustin, you're cutting out.
达斯汀  你信号不好
- Mike? - Dustin, you there?
-迈克  -达斯汀  你在吗
Mike? Mike, do you copy?
迈克  你收到吗
Dustin...
达斯汀
[POWERING DOWN NOISE]
Shit! Not now. Please, not now. Mike!
该死  别现在啊  别啊  迈克
- Dustin! - Mike!
-达斯汀  -迈克
[STATIC HISSING]
What is it?
怎么了
Do you have any batteries? Double-A?
你有电池吗  双A的
Why would I have batteries?
我怎么会有电池
I always carry batteries.
我总随身带电池
Then what's the problem?
那有什么问题
I need eight.
我需要八个
Eight?
八个
Shit. Guess we'll have to go to plan B.
该死  我们得启用B计划了
Plan B? What's plan B?
B计划  那是什么
[FILM SCORE CRESCENDOS]
Where... are they?
他们人呢
That's amazing.
太棒了
So, like, I wasn't totally focused in there or anything, but...
我刚刚并没有 非常全神贯注  但是
I'm pretty sure...
我确定
that mom was trying to bang her son.
那妈想上她儿子
Wait, wait, the hot chick was Alex P. Keaton's mom?
等等  那个性感小妞是艾利克斯·基顿他妈吗
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
是啊  我确定是的
But they're the same age.
但他们同龄啊
No, but he went back in time.
不  他穿越时间了
[SNICKERS]
Then why is it called Back to the Future?
那为什么要叫《回到未来》
He has to go back to the future
他得回未来去
because he's in the past.
因为他在未来
So, the future is actually the present,
所以未来就是现在
which is his time.
他的时代
Wh... What?
什么
No, no, it's my turn. You've had enough.
不  该我了  你喝够多了
[ROBIN GRUNTS CONTENTEDLY]
[GENTLE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[ECHOING] Wow.
[TWINKLING]
[ECHOING] Hey, Robin.
罗宾
You gotta check this out.
你会想看看的
- [GRUNTS] - Check this...
看啊
This... The ceiling, it's beautiful.
天花板  好美啊
[ECHOING] Oh, wow.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh.
[ROBIN CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
[STEVE GROANS]
[SYNTH MUSIC DISTORTS]
[TWINKLING]
[STEVE GRUNTS]
[ROBIN COUGHS]
[ROBIN RETCHES AND SPITS]
[CHEERING]
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[HOPPER YELLS]
Stay here, go over the plans with Smirnoff.
待在这里  跟司木露过一遍计划
- I can help look. - No, you'll scare the children.
-我能帮忙找  -不  你会吓到孩子
- Jim, if this is about earlier... - Stay put, Freud!
吉姆  如果是为了之前的事 别走开  弗洛伊德
You hear me? Stay put!
听到了吗  别动
[MURRAY SIGHS]
[KIDS SCREAMING AND LAUGHING]
You know, say what you will about Kline,
不管你怎么说克莱恩
he certainly knows how to throw a party.
他可真会开派对
I'm sorry about him, by the way.
我替他道歉了
- Who, Larry? - No, Murray.
-谁  拉里吗  -不  莫里
He's a sick individual who likes to get under people's skin.
他就是个变态  喜欢惹人生气
So, let's not let him, you know, get under our skin.
别让他惹我们生气
I'm not, I haven't.
我没有
I just, you seem a little more quiet than usual.
你似乎比往常更安静了
- I just... I just wanna find the kids. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-我只想找的孩子们  -好
[LARRY] I'll give it my best shot.
我努力一试
- [BELL CLANGING] - [LARRY EXCLAIMS]
[MAN] You won yourself a bear!
你赢了只熊
Thank you. Here you go. [CHUCKLES]
谢谢  给你
[PHOTOGRAPHER] Mayor Kline!
[PHOTOGRAPHER] One more, one more.
克莱恩镇长  再来一张
[PHOTOGRAPHER] Big smile. There we go.
好好笑  好的
[CHEERING]
- Watch it! - [MAN 2] Happy Fourth, dick.
-小心  -国庆节快乐  混蛋
- [PANTING] - [DIALING ON CAR PHONE]
[LINE RINGING]
Come on, come on, come on!
快快快
Pick up, pick up, pick up, you commie bastards!
接听啊  你们这群共党混蛋
布拉德利大块头
[OMINOUS SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[FREEZER HUMMING]
[PULL-TAB CLICKS LOUDLY]
- [WHISPERS] Quiet. - [WHISPERS] Oh, sorry.
-安静  -抱歉
- How do you even drink that? - Because it's delicious.
-你怎么能喝那个  -因为好喝
[MIKE AND MAX] What?
什么
It's like Carpenter's The Thing.
就像卡朋特的《怪形》
The original is a classic,
原版是经典
no question about it.
毫无疑问
But the remake...
但翻拍
[SLURPING LOUDLY]
[SATISFIED SIGH]
[SMACKING LIPS]
Sweeter, bolder...
更甜  更大胆
better.
更好喝
You're insane.
你疯了
So, you prefer the original Thing?
那你更喜欢原版《怪形》吗
What? No, I'm not talking about The Thing,
什么  不  我不是说《怪形》
I'm talking about New Coke.
我是说新可乐
It's the same concept, dude.
概念是一样的  哥们
Uh, actually, it's not the same concept.
其实  才不是呢
It is the same concept.
就是的
- No, it's not. - [YELLS] Yes, it is.
-不是的  -是的
Hey.
Sorry.
抱歉
Did you... find him?
你找到他了吗
[LUCAS] The movies?
电影院
Dustin's so freaked out about the gate,
达斯汀被入口的事吓坏了
he decides to go watch a movie?
于是决定去看电影吗
Yeah, makes total sense.
是啊  非常合理
You're positive he said "gate" and not "great"?
你确定他说的是"入口"不是"好"吗
Yeah, like, "This movie I'm watching is great."
是啊  比如"我看的电影好棒"
Sounded like "gate".
听上去像"入口"
Which would explain how the Mind Flayer's still alive.
那就怪不得吸灵魔还活着了
- Yeah, we just have to shut it again. - Then the monster dies.
是啊  我们只需要再关上入口一次 然后怪物就死了
But if not, we always have Lucas's fireworks.
如果不行  我们还有卢卡斯的烟花
Keep mocking my plan, Max. Keep mocking it.
继续嘲讽我的计划吧  麦克斯
I wanna hear you say it again, because you keep doubting me.
我想再听你说一次  因为你总质疑我
You keep doubting me!
你总质疑我
- [MAX] Ridiculous. - [LUCAS] Will?
-荒唐  -威尔
We're gonna prove 'em wrong, right?
我们能证明他们错了  是吧
[EERIE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREECHING]
[STEVE GROANS]
The ceiling stopped spinning for me.
天花板不转了
Is it still spinning for you?
你呢
Holy shit.
我去
No.
不转了
You think we puked it all up?
你觉得我们都吐出去了吗
Maybe. Ask me something.
可能吧  问我点什么
[IN RUSSIAN ACCENT] Interrogate me.
审讯我
Okay. Interrogate you. Sure.
好  审讯你  好啊
Um...
When was the last time you, uh, peed your pants?
你最后一次尿裤子是什么时候
Today.
今天
What?
什么
When the Russian doctor took out the bone saw.
苏联医生掏出骨锯的时候
[LAUGHS] Oh, my God.
天呐
It was just a little bit, though.
就尿了一点点
Yeah, it's definitely still in her system.
是啊  她还没排净呢
[LAUGHS]
[GROANS]
[ROBIN] Oh...
- All right, my turn. - Okay.
-好了  换我  -好
Hit me.
说吧
Have you...
你...
ever been in love?
爱过什么人吗
Yep. Nancy Wheeler.
爱过  南茜·维勒
First semester, senior year.
高四第一学期
[IMITATES GUNSHOT, CHUCKLES]
Oh, my God.
天呐
She's such a priss.
她好娇气啊
[STEVE] Hm.
Turns out, not really.
其实  并不
[SCOFFS] Are you still in love with Nancy?
你还爱着南茜吗
- No. - Why not?
-没有  -为什么
I think it's because I found someone who's a little bit better for me.
可能是因为我找到了 更合适我的人
[CHUCKLES] It's crazy.
好疯狂
Ever since Dustin got home, he's been saying,
自从达斯汀回来  他一直在说
"You know, you gotta find your Suzie. You gotta find your Suzie."
"你得找到自己的苏茜"
Wait, who's Suzie?
等等  苏茜是谁
It's some girl from camp, I guess his girlfriend.
夏令营的姑娘  好像是他女友
To be honest with you, I'm not 100% sure she's even real.
老实说  我不确定她是真实存在的
But that's not... that's not really the point.
但那不是重点
That doesn't matter. The point is, this girl,
不重要  重要的是
you know, the one that I like,
我喜欢的那个女孩
it's somebody that I... didn't even talk to in school.
她是我上学时从未注意过的人
And I don't even know why.
真不知为什么
Maybe 'cause Tommy H. would've made fun of me or...
或许是担心被汤米·H嘲笑
I wouldn't be...
或是担心我当不上
prom king.
舞会国王
It's stupid. I mean, Dustin's right,
真蠢  达斯汀是对的
it's all just a bunch of bullshit anyways.
那全都是扯淡的
Because, when I think about it,
因为  想起来
I should've been hanging out with this girl the whole time.
我就该一直跟她玩的
First of all, she's hilarious. She's so funny.
首先  她很风趣幽默
I feel like, this summer, I have laughed harder
这个夏天  我好久
than I have laughed...
都没笑得
in a really long time.
那么开心了
And she's smart.
她还聪明
Way smarter than me.
比我聪明多了
You know, she can crack, like, top secret Russian codes and...
她能破解绝密苏联密文
You know? She's honestly unlike anyone I've ever even met before.
她显然不像我认识的任何人
Robin?
罗宾
[TAPPING ON STALL]
Robin, did you just OD in there?
罗宾  你是服药过量了吗
No. [SIGHS]
没有
I...
我
am still alive.
还活着
[DEEP SIGH]
[ROBIN] The floor's disgusting.
地板好恶心
Yeah, well, I already got a bunch of blood
是啊  我衣服上反正
and puke on my shirt, so...
也都是血和呕吐物了
What do you think?
你觉得怎么样
About?
什么
This girl.
这个女孩
She sounds awesome.
她听上去很棒
She is awesome. And what about the guy?
她是很棒  那男人呢
I think he's on drugs, and he's not thinking straight.
我觉得他嗑药了  脑筋不清醒
Really? 'Cause I think he's thinking a lot more clearly than usual.
是吗  我可觉得 他脑子比平常清醒多了
He's not.
不是的
Look...
听着
he doesn't even know this girl.
他根本不了解这个姑娘
And if he did know her,
如果他真了解她
like... like really know her,
真的了解她
I don't think he'd even want to be her friend.
我觉得他都不会想跟她做朋友
No, that's not true. No way is that true.
不  不是的  这是不可能的
Listen to me, Steve.
听我说  史蒂夫
It's shocked me to my core,
虽然让我很震惊
but I like you.
但我喜欢你
I really like you.
我真的很喜欢你
But I'm not like your other friends.
但我不像你的其他朋友
And I'm not like Nancy Wheeler.
我也不像南茜·维勒
Robin, that's exactly why I like you.
罗宾  所以我才喜欢你
[ROBIN SCOFFS]
Do you remember what I said about Click's class?
你记得我说的  滴答老师的课吗
About me being jealous and, like, obsessed?
关于我的嫉妒  执迷
Yeah.
嗯
It isn't because I had a crush on you.
不是因为我喜欢你
It's because...
是因为
she wouldn't stop staring at you.
她总盯着你看
Mrs. Click?
滴答老师吗
[CHUCKLES]
Tammy Thompson.
塔米·汤普森
I wanted her to look at me.
我希望她看我
But... she couldn't pull her eyes away from you
但她的眼睛就是死死盯着你
and your stupid hair.
和你讨厌的头发
And I didn't understand, because you would get
我不能理解  因为你总把百吉饼碎屑
bagel crumbs all over the floor.
撒一地
And you asked dumb questions.
你还提愚蠢的问题
And you were a douchebag.
你还是个混蛋
And... And you didn't even like her and...
你都不喜欢她
I would go home...
我会回到家
and just scream into my pillow.
冲我的枕头里吼
But Tammy Thompson's a girl.
但塔米·汤普森是个女孩
[SOFTLY] Steve.
史蒂夫
Yeah?
怎么
Oh.
Holy shit.
我去
Yeah.
是啊
Holy shit.
我去
Steve...
史蒂夫
did you OD over there?
你是服药过量了吗
No, I just, uh...
不  我就是
just thinking.
在想
Okay.
好吧
I mean, yeah.
是啊
Tammy Thompson, you know, she's cute and all, but...
塔米·汤普森  她是挺可爱
I mean,
但是
she's a total dud.
她好没用
She is not.
才不是呢
Yes, she is. She wants to be, like, a singer.
就是  她想做个歌手
She wants to move to, like, Nashville and shit.
还想搬去纳什维尔
- She has dreams. - She can't even hold a tune.
-她有梦想  -她唱歌跑调
She's practically tone-deaf. Have you heard her?
她基本上是音痴  你听过她唱歌吗
- [ROBIN CHUCKLES] - All the time.
总是跑调
[SINGING ATONALLY] ♪ You see me now tonight ♪
*你今晚看到我*
- Shut up. - ♪ You see me... ♪
- She does not sound like that. - She sounds exactly...
-闭嘴  -*你看到...*
-她唱歌才不是那样呢  -就是的
- That's a great impersonation of her. - She does not.
-我模仿得可像了  -她才不呢
You sound like a Muppet.
你听上去像布偶
She sounds like a Muppet.
是她像
She sounds like a Muppet giving birth.
她像生孩子的布偶
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SINGS LIKE KERMIT] ♪ And if you could hold me tight ♪
*如果你可以紧紧抱住我*
[BOTH SING ATONALLY] ♪ We'll be holding on forever ♪
*我们会永不放手*
- Exactly. - [LAUGHS] I know!
-是吧  -说得对
Okay.
好了
What the hell?
搞什么
[BOTH LAUGH]
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[CREATURE SHRIEKS WEAKLY]
[MONSTROUS SCREECHING]
[CHEERING AND LAUGHING]
[ALEXEI, IN RUSSIAN] And why all this?
这是干什么
If I just turn the keys, it's like turning off a car.
如果我关闭钥匙  就像关闭一辆车
But then the car still works, does it not?
但车还是好用的  是吧
[IN RUSSIAN] Yes.
对
And do you want the car to still work or do you want it to explode?
你是希望车 还能用呢  还是希望它爆炸
I want the car to explode.
我希望车爆炸
Good. Then do this.
很好  那就这样办
Just make sure you are nowhere near it when it does.
只需要确保 车炸的时候你不在附近
It is not pretty.
场面会很可怕
Turns people into dust.
人会被烧成渣
And then...
然后
It's over.
就结束了
[CHUCKLES]
And I become an American citizen and join in the fun, yes?
我可以成为美国人  也这样享受欢乐  是吧
Who said you had to be an American to join the fun?
谁说你得是美国人才能享受欢乐的
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[IN RUSSIAN] It doesn't get more American than this, my friend.
没有比这更美国的了  朋友
Fatty foods, ugly decadence,
肥胖食物  丑陋的堕落
rigged games...
被操纵的游戏
[IN ENGLISH] Fifteen tickets, please.
50张票  谢谢
[CHEERING]
- They are rigged, these games? - [IN RUSSIAN] Yes.
-游戏都是被操纵的吗  -对
[BALLOON POPS]
They do not look rigged.
看上去不像啊
That's just it, my dear Alexei.
就是这样  亲爱的阿列克西
They have been designed to present the illusion of fairness!
他们被设计成有公平的幻象
But it's all a scam, a trick,
但都是骗人的把戏
to put your money in the rich man's pocket.
为了让你掏钱给有钱人
That, my dear friend, is...
这  我亲爱的朋友
America.
就是美国
But, hey...
但是
knock yourself out.
请便吧
[CARNIVAL BARKER YELLING]
Where are you going?
你去哪
To get us the closest thing to food I can find.
去给咱俩找最接近食物的东西
Hey. Hey.
[JOYCE] Karen.
凯伦
[CARNIVAL BARKER] Step right up!
上来吧
[KAREN] ... feel the wind push you back and it's gonna...
感受风推动着你
- [TED] Hold on. Do we have seat belts? - Hey, Karen.
-等等  有安全带吗  -凯伦
Joyce!
乔伊
Oh, my gosh! How funny to see you here!
天呐  能见到你真是太好了
Where are the kids?
孩子们呢
I... I haven't seen them. I don't think they're here yet.
我没见到他们  他们好像还没来
- You three, up against the wall! - No, where are they?
-你们三个  靠墙  -不  他们在哪
Oh, my gosh, I can hardly keep track these days.
天呐  我现在都记不住了
Uh, they were at, uh...
他们去了...
Dustin's, then Lucas's,
达斯汀家  然后是卢卡斯家
- then Max's. - Max...
-然后是麦克斯家  -麦克斯
- You know how it is. Summer! - [ALARM BLARING]
你知道的  夏天嘛
Probably getting into some kinda trouble.
可能又去惹什么麻烦了
[RIDE DOOR WHIRRING]
Last warning, you two. Up against the wall!
最后警告  你俩  靠墙
Hold the ride!
别开机
On your life, Magnum.
后果自负  大块头
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
[TED MURMURS]
Woo! Here we go!
开始咯
Holy smokes!
我的老天
[TED] Holy smokes!
老天啊
[RAPID CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOC] Roads?
路
Where we're going, we don't need roads.
我们要去的地方  不需要有路
[CHEERING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[DOOR HINGE CREAKING]
[DUSTIN] And...
好了
blend.
融入
[WOMAN] It is so good!
太棒了
- Well, shit, that worked. - Course it worked.
-成功了  -当然
We just have to get on the bus with the rest of these plebes,
我们只需要跟其他平民一起上大巴
and home sweet home, here we come.
然后就回家了
- Uh, Dustin? - What?
-达斯汀  -怎么了
Yeah, we might not wanna go to your house.
我们最好别去你家
Why?
为什么
Well, I might've told them your full name.
我可能把你的全名告诉他们了
- What is wrong with you? - Dude, I was drugged.
-你什么毛病  -哥们  我被下药了
- So? - So?
-那又如何  -什么
So, you resist. You tough it out. You tough it out like a man.
你抵抗啊  撑过去  像个男人那样
Oh, yeah, it's easy for you to say.
是啊  你说得轻巧
Guys?
伙计们
Sorry for the inconvenience. Have a pleasant evening.
抱歉打扰  祝您晚上愉快
Abort.
放弃
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Abort. Abort.
放弃  放弃
[PANTING]
[STEVE] Shit.
该死
[ROBIN] Okay.
好吧
[STEVE] Come on, let's go, let's go.
快走
[ONLOOKERS CHEERING]
That's three green!
三个绿色
And here's dart number four!
第4个飞镖
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHEERING]
One more for the big prize!
再来一个  就能拿到大奖
You can do it, mister!
你可以的  先生
- [BELL RINGING] - [LOUD CHEERING]
[MAN] We have a winner!
有赢家了
[BARKER] Step right up, ladies and gentlemen!
来吧  女士们先生们
Get your tickets right here!
在这里买票
Murray!
莫里
看啊
[IN RUSSIAN] Look!
It's not rigged!
没被操纵
Ah!
[LAUGHS LIKE WOODY WOODPECKER]
It's not rigged.
没被操纵
[MURRAY LAUGHS HEARTILY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[CARNIVAL AUDIO FADES]
[SILENCED GUNSHOT]
[IN RUSSIAN] Traitor.
叛徒
[FAINTLY] Alexei!
阿列克西
[FEEDBACK WHINING]
[CLOWN'S LAUGHTER ECHOING IN SLOW MOTION]
[RESUMING NORMAL VOLUME] Alexei!
阿列克西
[CARNIVAL AUDIO RESUMES]
[IN ENGLISH] Oh, no. Oh, my God. Let's go.
不不  天呐  我们走
[ALEXEI GRUNTS AND COUGHS]
- Easy. - [ALEXEI GROANS]
慢点
[IN RUSSIAN] Keep pressure on it.
摁住了
I'll get you help.
我去找人帮忙
I'll get help.
[SUSPENSEFUL SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Jim... Jim.
吉姆
Jim!
They got Alexei, Jim!
他们打伤了阿列克西  吉姆
Jim! Alexei! They got Alexei, Jim!
吉姆  阿列克西 他们打伤了阿列克西  吉姆
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
We gotta go.
我们得走了
- We gotta go. - What?
-我们得走了  -什么
[HOPPER] Let's go.
快走
They make an odd couple, don't they?
他们真是奇怪的一对  是吧
Well, it's like they say,
就像人说的
there's someone for everyone.
谁都能找到适合自己的人
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL RINGING]
[KAREN SIGHS DEEPLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD EXCLAIMS]
[MALE VENDOR] Who wants a hot dog?
谁想要热狗
Find Murray, get the car,
找到莫里  上车
- bring it around back. - Okay.
-开到后面来  -好
[RECORDING OF CACKLING LAUGHTER]
[IN RUSSIAN] Heading to "Big Top".
前往"高顶"
Northeast side of the fair.
园游会东北区
[CARNIVAL BARKER] Step right up, ladies and gentlemen!
快上来  女士们先生们
Get your tickets to the Big Top here!
在这里买"高顶"的票
[BARKER SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY] ...this side of the Mississippi.
...密西西比州这边
Hey! Get your kids outta here! Police!
快带孩子离开  警察
Get 'em out of here! Go!
快带他们离开
[BARKER] You, sir!
-快走  -你  先生
Step on up!
快来吧
I see you eyeing the maze!
我看到你瞄着迷宫了
Don't be surprised! Don't be scared!
别意外  别害怕
[CROWD CHEERING]
[BARKER] Step on up, sir!
上来吧  先生
[RECORDING OF CACKLING LAUGHTER]
[EERIE MALE VOICE] Do you dare enter the cave of horrors?
你敢踏进恐怖洞吗
You never know what you might find around the corner.
你无从知道转个角会发现什么
[RECORDING OF EERIE GIGGLING]
Don't show your fear in the presence of the tiger.
别在老虎面前显露恐惧
[TIGER'S ROAR SOUNDS]
Or you may never escape this cave alive.
否则你可能别想活着逃出去了
- [TIGER'S ROAR SOUNDS] - [HOPPER YELLS]
[FIGHTING GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
Alexei!
阿列克西
Oh, my God.
天呐
I... I just left for a minute...
我就离开了一下
for a corn dog.
去买玉米热狗
- [JOYCE CRIES] - A stupid corn dog.
该死的玉米热狗
Oh, God.
天呐
Oh, no.
不
- [MAN GRUNTS] - [CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[FIGHTING GRUNTS]
[MAN GROANS]
[HOPPER YELLS]
[HOPPER GRUNTS]
[MAN WAILS IN PAIN]
[MAN GROANS]
[HOPPER YELLS]
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[PANTING]
[INDISTINCT MALE VOICE ON RADIO]
[MAN ON RADIO, IN RUSSIAN] Vasilev, are you there? Vasilev? Answer!
瓦西里  你在吗  瓦西里  回答
[MALE VOICE CONTINUES IN RUSSIAN]
[TIGER'S ROAR SOUNDS]
[RECORDING OF CACKLING LAUGHTER]
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing?
你在干什么
Hey!
- Larry. - Joyce.
-拉里  -乔伊
[JOYCE GRUNTS]
[LARRY WAILS IN PAIN]
Ooh! [GROANS]
[MAN] Yeah, lady!
好样的  女士
[SUSPENSEFUL SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[SILENCED GUNSHOTS]
[HOPPER] Hey.
[MEN SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[GASPS]
[RECORDING OF CACKLING LAUGHTER]
[GASPS FOR AIR, GROANS]
[GRIGORI COUGHS]
[MAN, IN RUSSIAN] Comrade!
同志
Get off me!
放开我
[RECORDING OF CACKLING LAUGHTER]
[SIGHS]
Goddamn!
该死
Son of a bitch!
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
Hey!
[HOPPER] Hit it. Hit it! Go! Go!
快跑  走
Alexei?
阿列克西呢
[MAN ON RADIO, IN RUSSIAN] On the lower level...
在下层
Hey, translate.
翻译
We've found the children.
我们找到孩子了
They are still in the mall. Lower level.
他们还在商场  下层
[IN RUSSIAN] Keep all entrances locked down.
封锁所有入口
I repeat...
重复
Keep all entrances locked down.
封锁所有入口
[SQUEAKING SOUND]
[QUIETLY] Everyone, get over here.
所有人  过来
I found them.
我找到他们了
[KIDS PANTING]
[PANTING]
- [CAR ALARM WAILING] - [ALL GASPING]
[HORN HONKING]
[IN RUSSIAN] What the hell?
搞什么
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[MEN GROANING]
[STEAM HISSING]
[METAL CLATTERING]
[DRAMATIC SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHING] You flung that thing like a Hot Wheel!
你丢那玩意就像丢风火轮一样
[DUSTIN GRUNTS]
- Lucas? - What are you doing here?
-卢卡斯  -你怎么在这儿
Ask them. It's their fault.
问他们啊  都怪他们
True, yeah. Totally true. It's absolutely our fault.
是啊  的确都怪我们
I don't understand what happened to that car.
我不懂那车是怎么了
El has superpowers.
一一有超能力
- [ROBIN] I'm sorry? - Superpowers. She threw it with her mind.
-什么  -超能力  她靠念力丢的车
- C'mon, catch up. - That's El?
-跟上  -她是一一
- Who's El? - I'm sorry, who are you?
-一一是谁  -抱歉  你是谁
- I'm Robin. I work with Steve. - She cracked the top secret code.
我是罗宾  史蒂夫的同事 她破解了绝密密文
Yeah, which is how we found out about the Russians.
我们就是这样发现了苏联人的事
Russians? Wait, what Russians?
苏联人  什么苏联人
- The Russians! - Those were Russians?
-苏联人  -那是苏联人
- Some of them. - What are you talking about?
-有些是  -你说什么呢
- Didn't you hear our code red? - Yeah.
-你们没听到我们的红色警报吗  -嗯
- Couldn't understand what you were saying. - Goddamn low battery.
-但我根本听不懂  -该死的电池
How many times do I have to tell you with the low battery?
这事我都跟你说多少次了
Well, everything worked out, didn't it?
这不一切都好吗
- Worked out? We almost died. - Yeah, but we didn't, did we?
都好  我们差点死了 是啊  但我们不是没死吗
- [STEVE] It was pretty damn close. - [LUCAS] Okay, Russians?
-挺悬的了  -好吧  苏联人
As in, they're working for the Russian government?
他们是在为苏联政府工作吗
- [ELEVEN PANTING] - [DUSTIN] What are you not comprehending?
你是哪里不理解
Am I not speaking English?
我说的不是英语吗
- We have a full-blown Red Dawn situation. - [DRONING SOUND]
现在完全是《红色黎明》的情况
[MAX] So this has nothing to do with the gate?
这跟大门无关吗
[DUSTIN] It has everything to do with the gate...
跟大门非常有关
[DRONING SOUND INTENSIFIES]
[ELEVEN GRUNTS, GROANS]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- El! El! - [WHIMPERING]
一一
- [ERICA] What's wrong with her? - What's wrong?
-她怎么了  -怎么了
My leg. My leg.
我的腿
Her leg, her leg. Okay.
她的腿  好吧
[ELEVEN PANTING]
- Get that off. - Okay.
-拿掉  -好
[ALL EXCLAIM IN DISGUST]
[ERICA GROANS]
[GASPS]
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
[WAILING]
El! El!
一一
[WAILING]
[MIKE] El! El, are you okay?
一一  你没事吧
El! El!
一一
El!
☆谢谢观赏☆
喜马拉雅主播 & 微信公众号:
美国青少年英语
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
[SCREAMING]
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[MONKEY SCREECHING]